http://www.islandheritage.co.uk/privacy-policy

HomeAbout UsPaintingsMarine ArtMary Fedden RADeryck Foster RSMARichard GrantKen Howard RACavendish MortonMervyn PearsonMartin SwanFred YatesPrintsCarry AkroydEdward Bawden RAClare Curtis Mary Fedden RAMark Hearld Emily Sutton Objets d'artPoole Studio PotterySamuel Saunders PotteryTrench ArtCollectablesTroikaTransportIsland BooksLimited EditionRare Art BooksSt. Ives SchoolSculptureArt CataloguesPottery & CeramicsIndustrial & LocalRailways & ShippingJ Samuel White LtdContact & Opening TimesMoreHomeAbout UsPaintingsMarine ArtMary Fedden RADeryck Foster RSMARichard GrantKen Howard RACavendish MortonMervyn PearsonMartin SwanFred YatesPrintsCarry AkroydEdward Bawden RAClare Curtis Mary Fedden RAMark Hearld Emily Sutton Objets d'artPoole Studio PotterySamuel Saunders PotteryTrench ArtCollectablesTroikaTransportIsland BooksLimited EditionRare Art BooksSt. Ives SchoolSculptureArt CataloguesPottery & CeramicsIndustrial & LocalRailways & ShippingJ Samuel White LtdContact & Opening TimesHomeAbout UsPaintingsPrintsObjets d'artIsland BooksContact & Opening Times
Privacy PolicyGrey Funnel requires a minimum amount of personal information about its customers for the purpose of processing orders and answering requests for further information made through our website. The information we need to collect about you is securely held to protect your privacy. Information we Hold.We only hold information about you that you have provided to us. This will be used by us only for the purpose of processing an order, an on-line order, contacting you in relation to the progress of an order or in response to a request for further information made through our website. We hold the following personal information when processing an on-line order:a) Your name and postal address. b) Your phone number and e-mail address.We assume that you agree that we may obtain and hold this information for the purposes stated above. Payment InformationWhen you make a card payment it will be securely processed through PayPal which will require credit or debit card details. All your financial information (like your bank account details and your credit card number) are securely stored and encrypted on PayPal servers and is not shared with us. Protection of Personal InformationGrey Funnel do not share, sell, rent, distribute or transfer your personal information by any means to or with third parties unless your prior consent has been given. Further Information.If you have any questions or concerns relating to our Privacy Policy then please e-mail us at privacy@greyfunnel.com
Copyright © 2020 Grey Funnel - All Rights Reserved.GREY FUNNEL® , GREY FUNNEL LINE®  &  TREWYN STUDIO®  are registered trade marks.Opening hoursPrivacy PolicyTerms & ConditionsCookie Policy
